脂肪少了六成  价格降了两成
At 60% less fat and 20% less price, The only thing
唯一不变的是扣伯家庭装火腿包的味道
Kolb Family Family Pack Ham Packs don't have less of is flavor.
火~~腿~~妞
Haaaaaaaaaaam, gurrrrl!.
家庭装火腿包  扣伯农场出品
Family pack ham packs, from Kolb Family Farms,
这家人肉到您很高兴
the family that's pleased to meat you.
火~~腿~~妞
Haaaaaaaaaaam, gurrrrl!
你不认识他是谁  可你知道他说的话
You don't know his name, but you know what he says,
喜爱他说话的方式
and you love how he says it.
火~~腿~~妞
Haaaaaaam gurl!
火腿热潮  席卷全球
引领这一切的男人究竟是谁
So, who is the man who started it all?
本·昌  今天非常荣幸能请到您来
Ben Chang, and we have him here with us today.
你就是火腿妞的创始人
You are the Ham Girl guy.
名人
炸到
对  我就是喊火腿妞的
Yes, I am the Ham Girl guy.
这一切怎么开始的
How did this happen?
我就是不断地去试镜  努力奋斗
Well, I just kept auditioning, you know, kept working hard.
现在呢
And now?
斯皮尔伯格都打电话了
Spielberg is calling.
哪里  我不信电话
Not you know, I don't go by phone calls.
信合约
I go by contracts.
可斯皮尔伯格考虑让你去演「蓝色」
But Spielberg is interested in you for The Color Blue.
是一部新的橡皮泥电影  对不对
In the new Play Dough movie, is that right?
或许  仅仅是或许
Maybe, you know, maybe.
但像我一直说的  生活就像过山车
But like I always say, you know, life is a roller coaster.
你原来是科罗拉多州一所社区大学的老师
You were a teacher at a community college in Colorado.
你是不是...
Did you just-.
-没错  -有一天上课的时候
- True. - One day in class say,
说下课  我要去好莱坞了
class dismissed, I'm headed to Hollywood?
我是说
I mean.
学生们是怎么反应的
How did your students react to that?
我还没怎么跟他们说上话
Well, you know, I haven't spoken to them, really.
我
I.
那里没什么值得我留恋的
There's not much for me back there.
没有朋友吗
No friends?
我比较独来独往
You know, I was kind of a loner,
大家会因此取笑我
people, you know, made fun of me for it,
我只好埋头工作  专心在自己的事业上
but I just kept my head down and stayed focused on my work.
他们现在可不会取笑了吧
Well they're making fun of you now, are they?
不会了  现在不会
No, they are not.
能给我表演一个火腿妞吗
Can I get a Ham Girl?
火~~腿~~妞
Haaaaaaaaaaam, gurrrrl!
不知道  这样吧就...
You know, I don't know if that was-.
就是这个味儿  女士们先生们
And there it is, ladies and gentlemen,
来自社区大学  成就小小成功
from community college to something a little bit better.
-关掉  -本·昌搭上了
- Turn it off. - Ben Chang is on a rocket ship
通往不朽名作的火箭
to eternal validation.
关  掉
Turn it off.
非常感谢您...
Thank's so much for being.
■
本字幕首发于字幕组网站
www.ZiMuZu.tv 欢迎交流
已经三周了
Well it's been three weeks.
我要把他的车拖走
I'm having his car towed.
翻  译    饭捣爱呆呆
翻  译    小泽玛丽裙
翻  译    仓井菜摇头咬唇娇喘雅蠛蝶
翻  译    铃木一橙挺腰抽气低吼一库走
时 间 轴    姜泽明步
后  期    东尼大骨头
校对/总监    铃木一橙
废柴联盟
第六季  第八集
致昌
To Chang.
祝你的成功转瞬即逝  冷宫永保你位
May your success be brief, and your colds last months.
杰夫
Jeff.
要么滚出格林德尔  要么跟我统一战线
Hey, get out of Greendale, or you get me in your corner,
二者不可兼得
you don't get both.
火腿妞
Ham, girl.
谁能想到昌会一举而红
Who would have predicted Chang becoming famous?
其实我真想过  记得吗
Technically, I did, remember?
不过我认为是由于
Only, I thought it would be for-.
吃掉某人  对
Eating someone, yeah.
你们觉得斯皮尔伯格那事是真的吗
You think that Spielberg stuff is really happening?
怎么可能嘛
How could that happen?
要真那样  世界不就都疯了
That would mean the world was insane.
火~~腿~~妞
Haaaaaaaaaaam, gurrrrl!
别嫌我俗  不过这样确实在经济上有好处
Not to be crass, but there is an upside to this, financially.
昌不在  让我们的保险金降了百分之六
Chang's absence lowers our insurance premiums 6%.
他离开只会是有利无弊
There's nothing but upsides to him leaving.
我们可能只是觉得有点被背叛了
I think we all just feel a little short changed.
在没人关注他的时候
We invested so much in him
我们为他付出了那么多
when no one else would.
因为我们都以为他已经疯到
Because we all assumed he was
如果被我们踢出去  他会死掉的
so insane he would die if we kicked him out.
结果这一切只是  我们在拖他后腿
This whole time it turns out we were holding him back.
我们本以为他是绊脚石
We thought he was bedrock.
没想到他其实是为我们遮风避雨的岩顶
But it turns out he was the ceiling of a cavern filled with us.
我已经准备好忘掉他的姓名了
I have already forgotten his name.
你真知道他叫什么吗
Did you ever really know his name?
那个中国人是吧
The Chinese fellow, right?
名字像个拟声词一样
Whose name was some kind of noise?
叮  咣  啷当
Clang, bang, merengue.
看来只有我高兴他不在了
Looks like I'm the only one who's not glad he's gone.
至少我终于可以腾点硬盘空间了
At least I can finally clear some space in my hard drive.
伦纳德已经在那里待了好一会儿了
Oh, Leonard's been in there for a while,
你要是想用女厕所  我去帮你看着
but I can stand guard if you wanna use the women's room.
不是  我是说在昌接火腿妞广告前
No, I mean, I was shooting a movie with Chang
我跟他一起拍的电影
before he booked Ham Girl.
之后他再也没联系过我
I haven't heard from him since,
所以我觉得那些镜头应该都没用了
so I assume the footage is useless.
他签过授权书了吗
Did he sign a release form?
当然
Sure.
做任何事之前  我都会让演员签授权书
I make all my actors sign releases before we do anything.
你永远不知道谁会...
You never know who is going to.
本校拥有一部火腿妞男出演的电影
The school owns a movie starring the Ham Girl guy.
很快就是斯皮尔伯格的火腿妞男了
Soon to be Spielberg's Ham Girl guy.
反正也没法拍完
There's no way to finish it, though.
阿布蒂
Abed?
关于放弃我是怎么教你的
What have I told you about quitting?
有时这是唯一可以活下去的方法
That it's sometimes the only way to survive.
别忘了我说的是  有时
Well, don't forget I said sometimes.
尤兰达  市长来找我麻烦了
Yolanda, the mayor's up my ass.
我要正义
I want justice.
让他进来
Get him in here!
这样对吗
Is that right?
我应该生气吗
Should I be angry?
电影里的英雄是正义警察
The film's hero is police justice.
有一位现实生活中的前警察帮我想台词
I had a real life former cop help me with the dialogue.
我要敲你心脏
I'm gonna punch you in the heart.
现实生活中的前警察台词功力比较差啊
Real life former cops aren't great with dialogue.
我觉得英雄不应该是警察
I don't think police should be heroes.
布雷塔  交房租
Britta, pay your rent.
抱歉  阿布蒂  我需要更多资料
Sorry, Abed. Okay, I need more information.
我的动机是什么
What's my motivation?
我结婚了吗
Am I married?
我需要更多信息才能继续
I need more to go on.
可以去吃午餐了吗
Can we get lunch?
好  卡
Okay, cut.
总共就这么多了
That's about all we got.
那天昌知道烤汁猪腿堡回归了
Chang found out the McRib was back
之后就啥也没干
and we lost the rest of the day.
好演员  大烤汁猪腿堡瘾
Great actor, huge McRib problem.
各位
Everybody.
这位就是我跟你们讲的朋友  莫里
This is my friend I told you about, Maury.
他是真正的好莱坞电影制片人  遵医嘱
He's a genuine Hollywood film producer whose doctor ordered him
因身体状况必须在科罗拉多州生活
to live in colorado due to a medical condition.
把跟我说的再跟他们说一遍
Tell them what you told me.
我血液中的氮素水平高入云霄
Yeah, my blood nitrogen levels are through the roof.
大多数时间  我不能...
Most of the time, I can't-.
不不  不对  另一个事
Oh, no, no the other thing.
好的  如果你能剪辑出
Oh, right. If you can cut together
一部由争议明星火腿妞男主演的
an 81 minute movie that arguably stars
81分钟的电影
the Ham Girl guy,
我跟你们保证  分账到手非常快
I can guarantee distribution and a fast turnaround deal.
大家都这么干
People do it all the time
用新星的老镜头剪辑
with old footage from recently famous actors.
看过范·迪塞尔在1996年的「乐裤子」没
Have you seen Vin Diesel in 1996's Happy Pants?
没
No.
范·迪塞尔也没看过
Well, neither has Vin Diesel,
但他电影学院的室友卖了五十万
but his roommate from film school saw 500 grand.
可我不能就这么把我的警察剧付之一炬
But,I can't just burn up my cop drama.
趁我还没有靠拍乱七八糟的东西来赚钱
It's my only chance at the mainstream success I need
这是我取得主流成功的唯一机会
before I'm allowed to make weird stuff for money.
这是我的「美国风情画」
It's my American Graffiti,
我的「象人」我的「四个房间」
my Elephant Man, my Four Rooms,
罗伯特·罗德里格兹片段
the Robert Rodriguez segment.
为什么一定要是警察剧
Well, why does it have to be a police movie?
现在大家都不爱看警察了
People don't even like police now.
大家喜欢恐龙  喜欢外星人
They like dinosaurs, they like aliens
和任何克里斯·帕拉特加入的队伍
and anything else that Chris Pratt can join forces with.
我手里只有一个三分钟的镜头
I have three minutes of footage and
很明显他就是纽约办公桌后的警官
he's clearly a police chief behind a desk in New York.
是吗  不是宇宙约吗  不是恐龙桌吗
Is he? Or is it Space York, or is it a dinosaur desk?
我怎么知道呢
How do I know?
加点CG特技
Just add some CG.
他们就是这么搞克里斯·帕拉特的
That's what they do with Chris Pratt.
先把他放进普通的场景里  然后加点怪物
They put in him a regular scene, and then they add some Gagoos.
我还真有几个怪物的CG模型
I have a few CG models of some Gagoos.
我被漱口水广告开除的时候了
I got fired from a mouthwash commercial,
但我成功夺回了我的牙龈炎怪兽版权
but I successfully won back the rights to my gingivitis monster.
还有不知道这么能不能帮上忙
Also, I don't know if it helps,
不过我挪房车的时候找到了这个
but, when I moved into my RV, I found this.
你们看到有什么特殊的地方了吗
Now, that, you notice anything strange?
台球里绿球没有3
There's no green three in billiards.
有绿球6和绿球14
Now, there's a green six and a green fourteen,
但没有绿球3
but never a green three.
那这个球是什么运动里的
So, what sport is this from?
它又怎么会出现在我的房车里
And why was it in my RV?
总之  我可以帮电影做点动画特效
Anyway I, I can do some CG for the movie.
你们得需要克里斯·帕拉特那样的男主
You'll need a Chris Pratt type.
「银河护卫队」星爵的扮演者
我可以上
I'll do it if I have to.
我也能扮慵懒范儿
I can slouch.
真不敢相信  你们居然在劝我同意
I can't believe you guys are the ones pitching me this,
而我自己都不敢相信  我要拒绝
and I can't believe I'm saying no.
不许拒绝
You're not saying no.
法律上  我是不能强迫你
I mean, legally,I can't force you.
不过我可以发布一个晨间公告
But, I can do a morning announcement
让你成为永远的众矢之的
that will make everyone hate you forever.
严格说来  阿布蒂  如果你不拍这部电影
Technically, Abed, you would be robbing the school
你会让学校损失五十万美金
for half a million dollars by not making this movie.
什么电影
But, what movie?
你刚没在听吗
Have you not been listening?
电影讲的是火腿妞男
The movie about the Ham Girl guy,
在他的太空办公室里对抗怪物的故事
in his space office fighting some Gagoos,
领头人是克里斯·帕拉特那一型的
led by Chris Pratt type,
主演是光膀子的杰夫瑞
played by Jeffrey without his shirt.
周末开拍
It shoots this weekend.
-对  -好吧
- Yeah. - Yeah?
不过最终的剪辑得由我来
Okay, but I get final cut,
而且得是精品
and it has to be a good movie.
同意  但即使拍得很烂
Agreed, but you have to finish that cut
你也必须在周一完成剪辑
by Monday, even if it's bad.
同意  但一定得是我眼中的精品
I agree to that, but it has to be good by my standards.
绝对的  不过即使烂到家
Absolutely, and also, if it's terrible,
也没人会在意
nobody will notice or care.
你们都会帮我吗
You guys are all gonna help me?
我们会一起完成一部佳作
And we're gonna make a good movie?
当然  也可能是烂片
Definitely, or a bad one.
一定会很烂的
Probably a bad one.
看来大家都同意了
I think we're all on the same page.
对  是的
Yeah. I guess so.
太棒了
Good.
那赶紧的吧  把这垃圾捯饬出来
So, let's crap out this piece of crap.
他这种态度让我很担心
That attitude concerns me.
格林德尔社区大学
电影部
出品
我需要更多信息
I need more information.
阿布蒂作品
我的动机是什么
What's my motivation?
星际船长大战银河入侵者
给我更多信息我才能继续
I need more to go on.
我是星际船长  我遨游在这星际间
My name is Chief Starr, and I am in the stars.
我是个大英雄
And I am the hero.
我应该活得更好
I deserve better.
您真是个天资卓越的飞行家  星际船长
You're a very gifted pilot, Chief Starr.
我是外太空的市长
I'm the Mayor of outer space.
为什么改变航向
Why are we changing course?
市长你个屎
The Mayor is up my ass.
父亲  我爱他
Father, I love him.
外面是什么
What in the space?
尤吧嘟吧嘟吧
Yooba dooba dooba.
我们被攻击了
We're under attack.
是谁  小绿怪
By whom, Glip Glop?
卡
Okay, cut.
为什么喊卡
Why are we cutting?
我觉得还不错啊
That felt good to me.
-换场吗  -有几处要调整一下
- Moving on? Stop. - Just a couple of adjustments.
让你说两点
Ugh, you get two.
飞船受到撞击的时候  你们要晃晃
You guys need to move when the ship gets hit.
要是不动  会显得很怪
It looks weird when you stand still.
还有布雷塔  你说话不出错  听着不对头
And Britta, it sounds weird when you use good grammar.
我的角色连话都说不好吗
My character can't have good grammar?
在宇宙战里不会
Not in a space battle.
因为我们的台词都好自然哦
Because everything else we're saying sounds really natural,
比如我是个太空议员
like I'm a Space Senator.
是太空市长
Space Mayor.
我要把你的台词和昌的对上
I'm matching your dialogue to what I have from Chang.
-我的台词呢  -你没有台词
- When are my lines? - You don't have any lines.
你是昌的替身
You're the backup Chang.
可昌的部分已经拍好了
But we have Chang's footage.
这个场景的角度对着昌的背影
This shot from that angle matches the back of Chang's shot.
昌是星际船长
Chang is Chief Starr.
是宇宙飞船的飞行员
He's the pilot of the spaceship.
布雷塔  你是子午线公主
Britta, you're Princess Meridian.
布雷塔娜
Brittana.
好吧  杰夫是她的爸爸  太空市长
Okay. Jeff is her father, the Mayor of Space,
你们现在遭到了攻击
and you guys are under attack.
开拍
Action!
外面是什么
What in the space?
尤吧嘟吧嘟吧
Yooba dooba dooba.
我们被攻击了
We're under attack.
好  卡
Okay, cut.
你们往哪儿看小绿怪呢
Where are you guys seeing Glip Glop?
可小绿怪就是个网球
That Glip Glop was a tennis ball.
加瑞特不是小绿怪吗
But, Garrett's not Glip Glop.
如果我是小绿怪
If I was Glip Glop,
我还用棍子拿着个网球干什么
why would I be holding a tennis ball on a stick?
我又为什么要穿这身呢
Why am I wearing a blouse?
这是科幻片  无所谓的
It's Sci-fi, it doesn't matter.
别这么说
Please don't say that.
我知道你不是真心的
I know you don't mean that.
网球是小绿怪
The tennis ball is Glip Glop,
而且请你们晃的时候方向一致
and please stumble in the same direction.
开拍  来了
Go! Action. Bang.
外面是什么
What in space?
嘟吧嘟吧嘟吧
Gooba, gooba, gooba.
我们被攻击了
We're under attack!
是谁  谁攻击
Who by? Who attack?
我  公主
Me princess.
是斯珀波菲人
The Sporborfians!
好了  我准备好了
Okay, I'm ready.
你们准备好了吗
Are you ready?
我们在旋转了吗
Are we rolling?
我们在旋转
We're rolling!
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
快去逃生舱
Get to the escape pod.
搞毛  你干嘛选这套戏服
Really? You picked that outfit?
布雷塔
Britta?
是子午线
It's Meridian.
-接着演  -真是疯了
-Keep going. - Insane.
你叫什么  大恩人
And, what is your name, Exploitia?
我是天蝎9号  我是个逗乐机器人
Scorpio Nine, I'm a pleasure droid.
错了  我不是刺客吗
No, I'm an assassin?
都是  接着演
You're both, keep going.
她是个逗乐机器人
She was a pleasure droid.
后来变成了刺客
She got turned into an assassin.
是我另一个女儿
She's my other daughter.
这是你妹妹
That's your sister.
快去逃生舱
Get to the escape pods.
然后我们快逃
And then, then we go.
这边
This way.
问问星际船长  杰夫
Check out Chief Starr, Jeff.
星际船长
Chief Starr?
怎么了
What?
我们地狱里再相会吧
I'll see you in hell.
什么
What?
市长  你个渣渣
Mayor, your ass is grass.
好了  卡
Okay, cut.
还有些地方我们可以改...
There are some things that we could-.
好了  换场伙计们
Okay. Moving on, people.
好  换场
Okay, moving on.
下一场戏是空间站的工厂休息室
Next shot, space station faculty lounge.
辛苦各位
Thank you.
阿布蒂  我觉得进度要加快了
Abed, we need to move a little faster I think.
我能不能以导演的身份向你解释一下
Can I just explain something as a filmmaker?
还是别了
I wish you wouldn't.
我希望你能看看我现在这幅样子
I wish you would look at what I was wearing,
然后什么都别说了
and let that be all the explanation you need
标准就是这样了
about where are standards should be.
但你得明白
But, do you understand
科幻片不是一个周末就能凑和出来的
that sci-fi films aren't usually improvised over a weekend
何况整个剧组根本没人真的在意
with a cast and crew that doesn't care?
我们在意的是想早点杀青
We care about finishing.
这部电影必须在周一完工
And, this has to be finished by Monday.
你要以这样的质量标准看
So, you're back into a level of quality from there.
让我现想个比方
Let me use a metaphor I can understand.
我每天都会锻炼
Every day, I work out.
真的吗
Really?
是的  因为我不像你是搞艺术的
Yes, because I'm not an artist like you,
但我的身材就是我的画布
but this is a kind of canvas.
虽然我每天用器材锻炼  但没有结束的一天
I work on it with equipment, but I will never really be done.
如果你真的想是可以的
You could be if you wanted, I mean-
没有停下的时候的
This will never be done.
克里斯·帕拉特就不会停  对吧
Chris Pratt's never gonna stop, is he?
我永远比不上他
He'll always be out there mocking me.
所以我也不会停
So, I can never stop.
就像你永远不会放弃电影梦
Just like you'll never stop making movies.
但我不会一辈子每分每秒都待在跑步机上
But, I don't stay on one treadmill my entire life,
看着那些给克里斯·帕拉特电影赞助的广告
staring at commercials for movies with Chris Pratt.
我把锻炼放入现实中
I take my work into the world.
我让它首映了  和世界共享
I premiere it, I share with the public.
不要固守自封  阿布蒂
Don't stay in the gym, Abed.
把这一条拍完  出去  把衣服脱了
Get this session done, get out there and get your shirt off.
明白没
Got it?
明白
Yes?
明白了
Yes!
准备  开始
Ready, let's do this.
我知道你在找你的朋友
I understand you are looking for your friend.
没错
Yeah.
-我是牛头怪  -啥
- I am Minotaur Man. - What?
太空里遇到个朋友不容易
Friends are hard to come by in space.
你最好带上这个  防身用
You'd better take this for protection.
这声音是我给你的枪发出来的
The sound coming from the gun I gave you
这枪有四万超瓦的激光
is 40,000 hyper watts of laser.
哎呀  没事没事
Oh, don't worry, don't worry about that.
我还能粘回去
I can put that back.
有时候我眼珠子会掉下来  因为我是机器人
Sometimes my eye falls off because I mean, I'm a robot.
小心
Watch out!
这个巴哈酒吧怎么样
How about this Baja,
大家对暴力都习以为常
everyone here is so accustomed to violence.
我想要  不是...
I need, any no-.
你是要朋友吗
Where your friends are?
对
Yeah.
不好意思  你不会想听到的
I'm sorry, but you're not gonna like this.
你的朋友们被那个
Your friends have been taken prisoner by Master,
德...古拉主人捉走了
Master Dracula.
真是狂野的西部啊
Wild West baby.
太空版的狂野西部
Space version of the Wild West.
卡
Cut.
好了
Okay.
我眼珠子掉了  不过我掩饰过去了
My eye fell off, but, but, but I, I covered it.
-完美  下一场  走廊戏  -好
- Perfect. Moving on, hallway. - Yes!
吃我一记
Take that!
太多了
This is crazy.
看我的
Here.
我要做这个
Let me do this.
干什么呢你
What are you doing?
你这么一搞  是个女人都不好做了
You make everything harder for all women when you do that.
我在即兴创作啊
I'm improvising.
你即兴创作个口袋不行吗
Improvise pockets.
你要不付房租就闭嘴
Pay your rent, or shut up.
看我的激光炸弹
Laser bomb!
尤吧嘟吧嘟吧  小绿怪好喜欢
Yooba Dooba dooba, Glip Glop like.
尤吧嘟吧嘟吧  尤吧嘟吧嘟吧
Yooba Dooba dooba, Yooba Dooba dooba, Yooba Dooba dooba.
所以机器人也说「尤吧嘟吧」吗
So the robot also says yooba dooba.
我不想吐槽
I'm not complaining.
是不是这里只要不是人
It's just that everyone who's not a person
就都说「尤吧嘟吧」
is saying "Yooba Dooba.".
没错  因为我就是太空间谍
Maybe it's because I'm a spy.
他是间谍
He's a spy.
我是个坏坏的间谍
I'm an evil spy.
打绿怪  他是间谍
Shoot Glip Glop's he's a spy.
小绿怪是间谍
Glop Glop's a spy?
我们即兴发挥
We went with.
好  打他  打他
Okay shot. Shot.
好了  现在他被打死了
Okay now that now that he's dead
只剩一只机器人了
and there's one robot left
-我们去找那个东西吧  -走啊
- let's go to the thing. - Go.
尤吧嘟吧嘟吧  尤吧嘟吧嘟吧
Yooba Dooba dooba, Yooba Dooba dooba, Yooba Dooba dooba.
太空垃圾
Space garbage.
看哪
Look!
我们要被压扁啦
We're gonna get crushed.
这里有没有妖怪呀
And is there a monster?
打死他又怎样
But so what?
我们要被压扁了
We're gonna get crushed.
我...爱你
I love you?
-我爱你  -她是你女儿好吗
- I love you. - That's your daughter.
-你才是我女儿啊  -对啊可是你说
- You're my daughter. - Yeah and you said
我俩是姐妹来着  白痴
we were sisters, dumb ass.
太激烈了
It's hot.
就像太空版的唐人街
It's like Chinatown in space.
我这英雄要出现了
And I'm the hero?
好耶
Yay!
放马过来吧
Let's do this.
好耶
Yeah!
他们得救啦
They're saved!
感受原力吧
Feel the force.
啥
What?
我感受不到原力
I don't feel the force.
因为他们不让
I'm not allowed to.
你问我感受啥
What do I feel?
我感受到德古拉的力量
I feel Dracula force.
我感受到德古拉的信号
I feel Dracula signals.
我要收了你的小命
Your ass is mine.
你刚才那点小伎俩
That last stunt you pulled
害得我六个壮士进了医院
put six of my best guys in the hospital.
你个疯子
Maniac.
疯子怎能与我并论
I'm more than a maniac.
我就是德古拉
I'm Dracula.
哎妈呀  哎妈呀
Jesus Christ, Jesus Christ,
我的天啊  神啊他被打死了
Oh my God, Jesus Christ they shot him.
我是谁
Who am I?
我的动机是什么
What's my motivation?
我说我所说  做我所做  所谓何故
Why am I doing or saying anything that I am saying or doing,
我要得到更多  比现在得到的更多
I need more, I need more than what I'm getting.
太不可思议了
That was incredible.
热烈祝贺
Congratulations.
片长多少
How long is it?
87分钟
87 minutes.
搞成81分钟的  要81分钟哦
Get it to eight one, that means 81.
我要打几个电话  我们要首映
I'll make some calls, we'll premiere this thing,
我们还要给你们学校开支票
and we'll get your school a check.
那我们要剪哪里的6分钟呢
So which six minutes should we cut?
杰夫死的那场  怎么样
Jeff's death scene probably, right?
哦对
Oh. Yeah.
-剪我的戏  -对  就在太空地牢那场
- Mine? - Yeah, in the space dungeon?
那场戏里又没有昌
There's no Chang in that.
杰夫那场有多长
How long is Jeff's death scene?
就是啊  有多长  我们真的好投入耶
Yeah, how long is it. We're really zeroing in on it.
你以为我害怕了吗
Do you think I'm frightened?
这些铁链是用伽倪墨得斯星的铁锻造的
These chains were forged from the iron of Ganymede.
还有这钢
And the steel,
我才不会告诉你他的下落
I'm not going to tell you where he is.
我宁死不从
I'd rather die.
这场戏看起来还是很重要的
Hm, it seems pretty important
他死都不出卖昌
he doesnt give doesn't give up Chang.
另外  他跟昌说的最后一句话是
I mean, otherwise the last thing he says to him is,
我会在地狱与你相会
I'll see you in Hell.
可是  他又不是电影的主角
It's not really a movie about him.
是没错  那剪你那段钢桶独奏怎么样
Yeah. Hm-hm. Well, what about your steel drum solo?
我觉得那段可不能剪
Oh, I don't think we should lose that.
那在小绿怪的星球上的
Well, what about the weird wedding ritual
那段超怪的婚礼呢
on Glip Glop's planet, huh?
好吧
Okay.
咱别捡了芝麻丢西瓜好吗
Let's not throw out the baby with the bath water.
我们别去搞小绿怪
We're not getting a frame of Glip Glop.
我们还是把午夜牛郎里的牛郎剪了吧
I mean, that's like cutting Cowboy out of Midnight Cowboy.
杰夫受死的戏份正好是  6分半
Jeff's death scene is six minutes 30 seconds.
-走你  -走你吧
- There you go.  - Oh, there you go.
好吧好吧  简单粗暴
Okay, cool. Easy enough.
剪辑之前我们可不可以
Should we, before we finish editing,
先把垃圾里的黄蜂赶出去
should we get those hornets out of the garbage?
那群大黄蜂
Those swarming hornets.
他不是认真的吧
Is that serious?
-他事先想好的吧  -想的够深远的啊
- Is he doing a bit - That's a long bit.
他是来真的
Oh, he's serious.
我们就坦然面对吧
Let's face it.
他在演戏的时候就挺明显的
It's pretty obvious when he's acting.
来吧
Let's do this.
哟哟哟  大家好
Yo, yo, yo. Howdy.
欢迎来到凯尔·比得曼的剪辑教程
Welcome to Kyle Beiderman's editing tutorials.
我是凯尔·比得曼
I'm Kyle Beiderman.
对  就是那个凯尔·比得曼
Yeah, that Kyle Beiderman.
别烦我  阿布蒂
Leave me alone, Abed.
一旦我看了这个剪辑教程
Once I've watched this tutorial on how editing works,
我就要拯救这部影片  力保它的灵魂
I'm gonna save this movie without removing its soul.
第一步
Step one.
怎样给你的素材贴标签
How to correctly label your files.
谁要学贴标签啦  快教我怎么剪
Nobody cares about labeling files, teach me to edit.
什么声音
What the hell was that?
你死开
You stay away!
这也是我的电影
This is my movie too!
这根本算不上是电影  简直就是一垃圾
It's not even a movie Jeff, it's a piece of crap.
人家有颗想变成好电影的心
That doesn't mean it can't be good.
这基本上也就是它的本质意义了
That's basically exactly what it means.
给我退下  阿布蒂
You stay away Abed.
我不开玩笑
I'm not kidding.
我个头大  我零血糖
I'm huge and I have zero blood sugar.
我把你弄死在这堆飞盘里  谁也不会找到你
I will kill you in these frisbees and nobody will ever find you.
好
Okay.
现在我们来熟悉一下用户页面
So now let's get familiar with the user interface.
赶紧教我怎么编辑
No, just teach me to edit.
逗你呢
Bazinga.
我要杀了你
I'm going to kill you.
你要掐死我啦
You're killing me!
早警告过你了
I told you!
你真的要弄死我啦
You're literally killing me.
-真的吗  -嗯
- For real? - Yes!
你疯了吗
Are you nuts?
你有病吗
What is wrong with you?
除了我  你们每一个人都想离开
Every single one of you was gonna leave here except for me.
特洛伊  雪瑞  安妮要去当主席
Troy, Shirley, Annie's gonna be President.
就连皮尔斯也死了
Even Pierce got to die.
昌要去好莱坞了
And Chang goes to Hollywood.
我们逼你制作有史以来最烂的电影
So, we force you to make the crappiest movie of all time,
然后我们又逼你把它做得更烂
and then we force you to make it even crappier.
我们看了  居然没那么烂
And we watch it, and it's still not even that bad.
而我的角色无意之中演得最兴奋的部分
And the part I accidentally got the most excited about
却是我们要剪掉的那七分钟
is the seven minutes we can cut.
你知道这意味着什么吗
Do you know what that means?
意味着我是个天才  大家都知道
It means I'm a genius, but we already knew that.
我终于知道  在我内心深处
I finally know in my heart,
我将会是留在这里的最后一个人
that I will literally be the last one of us here.
而且我知道「银河护卫队」里
And I know, they gave digital muscles
克里斯·帕拉特的肌肉是数码合成的
to Chris Pratt in Guardians of the Galaxy.
我看了「公园与游憩」
I watch Parks and Rec.
我看了  完全没有科学道理
I watched it. There's no scientific explanation for.
杰夫
Hm, Jeff.
今天你帮我学到了一些关于做电影的道理
You helped me learn something about film making today
我觉得大家都需要将其致用于生活中
that I think we all need to apply to life.
有计划是好事
It's okay to plan some stuff,
努力找寻自己的错误也不是不可以
and it's okay to figure out what we did wrong.
但我们的计划可能是毫无目的  终会失败
But our plans are randomly gonna fall apart
我们学到的教训也毫无意义  是个错误
and our lessons are randomly gonna be wrong,
但如果我们坚持开机
and if we just keep the cameras rolling
拍下各种废柴人生  最终
and shoot a lot of crap eventually
安妮会深探内衣  掏出激光炸弹
Annie is going to reach down her shirt and pull out a laser bomb.
这不是我写的  也不在我们的计划之中
I didn't write that, we didn't plan that.
一切都是上帝旨意
God made that happen.
这部电影是上帝之作  而且很烂
God made this movie, and it's dumb.
参演其中的我们也无比废柴
And we're dumb for being in it.
生活是一部糟烂  毫无意义和剧情的大电影
Life is a big, dumb, pointless movie with no story
结尾突变  英雄反被德古拉枪杀
and an abrupt ending where the hero gets shot by Dracula
而且还是幕后花絮里订午餐时
in the middle of a lunch order during an outtake.
但总有那个时刻  每过一段时间
But somewhere in there, every once in a while.
安妮深探内衣
Annie reaches down her shirt.
我们坚持开机
So we keep the cameras rolling,
把不喜欢的部分剪掉
and we edit out the parts we don't like,
不要再过多纠结克里斯·帕拉特
and we stop thinking about Chris Pratt so much,
因为这样并不健康
because it is not healthy.
帮我个忙好吗
Will you do me a favor?
咱俩的私密交谈我永远不会告诉任何人
I never tell anybody about our private conversations.
我根本不晓得怎么告诉别人
I wouldn't really know how.
把我那段糟烂表演从这部烂片里剪去吧
Let's cut my stupid scene out of this piece of crap.
那30秒我们该怎么加
Then what we need to add 30 seconds?
我有个主意
I have an idea about that.
我是谁
Who am I?
我的动机是什么
What's my motivation?
我说我所说  做我所做  所谓何故
Why am I doing or saying anything, I'm saying or doing?
我结婚了吗
But, am I married?
我要得到更多
I need more.
比现在得到的更多
I need more than what I'm getting.
你好  星际船长
Hello Chief Star.
我跟你说过了地狱再相会
I told you I'd see you in hell.
看看还有谁来了
And look who else is here.
尤吧嘟吧嘟吧
Yooba dooba dooba.
导演  阿布蒂·纳德尔
新结尾做得太棒了
Oh, great job you guys, on the new ending.
他俩真的在地狱相会了  我喜欢这段
I like that the guy actually saw him in hell.
赞哦
Right?
等下  有电话
Hold on, phone call
分销商打来的
from the distributor
准备好收一份巨额支票吧
get ready for a big check.
哈喽
Yellow.
等等  冷静一下
Wait. Calm down.
什么第十一章
What's Chapter 11?
等下  什么YouTube
Wait. What's YouTube?
等下  什么宽带
Wait. What's broadband?
什么数码
What's digital?
我对这个电话有种不好的预感
I don't have a good feeling about that call.
我对昌是否还有票房保证也有种不好的预感
I don't have a good feeling about Chang staying bankable.
你们看这个新闻报道了吗
Did you guys see this news story?
我以后再也无法直视热气球了
I'll never look at hot air ballooning the same way again.
詹姆斯·弗兰科大人的蛋蛋
Lord James Franco's balls.
别说了
Oh, no.
我告诉大家一个感觉好的事情
I tell you what I do have a good feeling about.
来抱抱
Bring it in.
来吧
Come on guys.
是哦
Yeah.
再拍一条  以防万一  本
All right, one more for safety Ben.
什么意思  什么以防万一
What do you mean, one more for safety?
我不知道有没有说那句台词
I, I just don't know if we get the line,
等一下  机灵鬼
hold on Slinky.
换场吧
Let's move on.
我觉得吧  咱们能再拍一条吗
I, I think, can, can we get one more?
好啦我说  等一下  机灵鬼
You got it! Come on! Hold on, Slinky!
撤了
Let's go.
我觉得挺好的  但斯蒂芬有点完美主义
I think it was fine, but Steven's kind of a stickler.
跟斯蒂芬·斯皮尔伯格说吃屎去吧
Tell Steven Spielberg to lick my butt.
他就在现场呢
Well, he's right here, so.
斯蒂芬·斯皮尔伯格
Hey, Steven Spielberg.
能稍等我们一下吗
Can you give us a sec?
好
Yes.
-本  -在
- Ben? - Yep.
我想今天这样就可以了
So, I guess we're good for today.
做得很好  你说得对  这些已经足够了
Great job, you were right. We got everything we need.
后面有个小门  就在隔间后面
And there's a small door in the back, back of the booth there,
你过了那个门  就是外面了
that will take you, you know, outside.
咱们回头再聊
And, we'll talk soon.
我不从来的时候那个门出去吗
I don't go the way I came?
不用
You do not.
后面有个小门  出门直接到外面
There is a little door back there, and it goes right on out.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
好
Okay.
-好  兰德尔  准备好了吗  -好了
- Okay, Randall, are you ready? - Yup.
下面是关于我校美容部的事宜
Which brings us to the issue of our cosmetology department,
他们再次发现自己
who once again, find themselves.
他们再次发现自己  接近学期末了
Who, once again, find themselves nearing the end of
依然没有任何免费的剪发志愿者
the semester without any free haircut volunteers.
原因可能是由于上学期的虱子恐慌事件
That may be due to last semesters lice scare.
-没错  -对
- Totally. - Yep.
如果我们树个标牌  保证没虱子
Maybe if we put up a sign, guaranteed no lice.
这样之类的
Something like that.
你会被起诉的
That would open you up to lawsuits.
孩子们  我们住在一个四面环墙的世界
Son, we live in a world that has walls,
墙壁守护者手持理发大剪刀
and those walls have to be guarded by men with hair clippers.
平克·弗洛伊德
Pink Floyd.
-你最烂了  -啥
- You're the worst. - What?
-她最烂了  -烂透了
- Oh, she is the worst. - Terrible.
-真不敢相信她会这么说  -烂啊
- I can't believe she said that. - Terrible.
说个电影
Name one movie.
布雷塔最烂
Britta's the worst!
■
最新美剧下载请登录字幕组网站
www.ZiMuZu.tv
扫描左边二维码关注我们的微信号
或搜索微信号: ustvboom
非常欢迎爱好者加入字幕组一起翻译海外影视剧
■
你看懂了吗
Did you get any of that?